It's her! I know it's her!
是她!我知道是她!
She wants to tell us something!
她有话要对我们说
We must do something! Please.
我们得有所行动
In the name of his Imperial Majesty and the city of Vienna,
我代表国王陛下与维也纳市
I hereby arrest Edward Abramowitz.
在此逮捕爱德华艾维兹
Also known as Eisenheim the Illusionist.
也就是魔术师艾森瀚
On charges of disturbing public order, charlatanism,
罪名是违反秩序
and threats against the Empire.
诈欺与危害安全
Leave him alone!
放开他
They're arresting him! They're arresting Eisenheim!
他们抓了他 他们逮捕艾森瀚
Chief Inspector Uhl.
乌尔探长求见
You're late.
你迟到了
My apologies, your Highness.
我很抱歉，王子殿下
I was attending to the loose ends of the case.
我还在努力解决一些问题
Are there still loose ends?
还有要解决的问题?
Very few.
不多了
Did he do it again?
他又表演了吗?
How does he do it?
怎么办到的?
I'm afraid I still don't know.
恐怕我还是不清楚
Did you ask him?
你没问他?
He's not talking at this point.
他此时什么都不肯说
Well, I'm sure you have methods for that kind of thing.
是吗，我相信你自有办法
I want you to put an end to it. Surely you have something on him.
我要你尽速结案 你怎么样都该有些线索
Something from his past?
有他的来历吗
Yes. Yes, I think I do.
是的，我查到了
In fact we know all about his life.
我们对他的一生了若指掌
We've spoken to almost everyone who ever knew him.
遍访每位认识他的人
As a boy, I'm told he had a chance encounter with a traveling magician.
他小时候曾遇见一位魔术师旅人
Boy.
孩子
One version of the story was that the man
其中一个版本是那人
himself then vanished along with the tree.
后来与树 一同消失了
Who knows what actually happened?
没人知道实际发生什么事
People began to think he had some kind of special power,
旁人开始相信他真拥有特殊能力
or at least that he was a bit different.
或是他的确与众不同
And then he met her.
接着，他遇见了她
Don't drop it.
别弄掉了
Careful, you're going to trip.
小心，你要摔倒啦
Drop it, you muck-snipe.
掉吧，你这穷酸鬼
Oh! Watch out for that hole, alley rat!
注意那个洞，臭小子
Drop it!
掉下来!
Pick a card. Put it back in the deck.
挑一张牌 把牌放回去
Now, watch.
现在，?看
Duchess Von Teschen, you can't be in a place like this.
特森女爵，?不能来这种地方
They're peasants. Remember who you are.
他们是粗人，记得?的身份
She was brought back to the castle and they were forbidden to see each other.
她被带回了城堡 两人还被禁止相见
But soon they were doing just that.
不久后，他们还是偷偷往来
Over the next few years they could always find a way to be together.
接下来几年，两人总有方法私会
Quick, come on.
快，快来
In China there's a magician that could make anything disappear.
中国的魔术师能把东西变不见
A house, a wagon, anything.
无论是房子、马车，什么都可以
We'll go visit him.
我们要去见他
They can't stop us if we want to be together.
他们不能阻止我们在一起
They'll never find us.
他们永远都找不到我们
Do you promise you'll take me with you?
你保证会带我一起走吗
One day I will.
总有一天，我会的
One day we'll run away together. We'll disappear.
有一天我们要一起逃离 我们会一起消失不见
There's a secret way to open it.
打开它是有秘诀的
I wanted a picture.
我想要这张照片
Sophie, are you there?
苏菲，?在那吗?
We must hurry! They're coming!
我们得快点!他们追来了!
Duchess von Teschen!
特森女爵!
Make us disappear.
让我们消失，让我们消失
Stop. Stop.
停下来
Don't do this. Let me go. Let go.
别这么做，让我走
No! Please, let go! No! Let her go, please!
不! 求求你，放手! 不! 放她走，求求你!
Let go! Stop it!
放手!停下来!
Sophie!
苏菲!
Eduard!
爱德华!
-Sophie! -Eduard!
-苏菲! -爱德华！
Sophie.
苏菲
Stay away from her or next time we'll arrest you and your family.
远离她，否则就抓你和你的家人
What happened next remains a mystery. We do know that he traveled the world.
后来发生的事仍是难解的谜 可确定的是他走遍世界
That he began to perform his magic in public.
当他开始公开表演魔术时
That he changed his name to Eisenheim.
改名为艾森瀚
And then almost fifteen years later he appeared in Vienna.
近十五年后，他在维也纳现身
Life and death, space and time, fate and chance.
生与死，空间与时间 命运与机遇
These are the forces of the universe.
以上都是宇宙的力量
Tonight, ladies and gentleman,
今晚，各位女士、先生
I present to you a man who has unlocked these mysteries.
容我介绍一位能解开宇宙奥秘
From the furthest corners of the world where the dark arts still hold sway,
远从世界尽头 来自?黑魔法仍主宰之处
he returns to us to demonstrate how nature's laws may be bent.
能扭转自然法则之人
I give you... Eisenheim.
请艾森瀚出场
Might I borrow a handkerchief from someone?
谁能借我一条手帕
You, Madam.
女士，就是?
Thank you. Ah, be patient.
谢谢? 请稍安勿躁
Now, if you please, I would like to continue with an examination of time.
现在，请容我来验证时间
From the moment we enter this life we are in the flow of it.
生命被注入的那刻起 只能任其发展
We measure it and we mark it but we cannot defy it.
我们能测量、标记，却无法违抗
We cannot even speed it up or slow it down.
无法加速或放慢
Or can we?
还是我们可以?
Have we not each experienced a sensation
我们都曾有过一种感受
that a beautiful moment seemed to pass too quickly?
美好时光过得特别快
And wished that we could make it linger?
总希望它能持续
Or felt time slow on a dull day
时间在无聊日子里过得特别慢
and wished that we could speed things up a bit?
希望可以加快
I assure you, they're quite real.
我保证它们是真的
And you, Madam, where is your handkerchief?
这位女士，?的手帕呢?
Bravo! Very good.
好极了!真精彩
Give us something. Please, please, give us something.
施舍我们 求求你，施舍我们东西
-Please. -What's all this?
-求求你 -怎么回事?
We're poor.
我们很穷
Do you think you're poor?
你们认为自己很穷?
Yes.
是的
I want to show you something. You're not poor.
我让你们看样东西 你们不贫穷
You have everything that you need right here.
这里有你们所需的一切
Thank you.
谢谢
And that's yours. And this too.
这是你的 这也是
-Good morning.
-早啊 -早安
-Coffee? -No.
-要咖啡吗? -不用
Strudel? I have two.
酥卷呢?我有两块
Nothing, thank you.
都不用，谢谢
You look very pleased with yourself.
你看来很怡然自得
How are the receipts?
票房如何
Not bad. A three-quarter house.
还不错，卖了四分之三
Well done.
做得好
But we're going to do better than that.
我们还会更好
Listen to this. Listen.
听听这个，听好了
"There is no argument that his uncanny displays separate
"无疑地，他神奇的演出
him from the ranks of garden variety stage wizards.
使他有别于随处可见的术士
Some of his effects transcend mere illusion and approach the realm of art.
他的部分演出甚至超越了幻象 已臻艺术之境
He is very young to be so masterful.
他年纪轻轻却已是大师"
You see? We'll pack the house with this review.
懂了吗，这评论包准让剧院满座
We are going to make more money than you ever dreamed of.
我们就要赚到超乎你想像的钱了
But if it was mechanical, maybe he had it wrapped in some kind of bark?
那是人造的，再用树皮包起来?
Oh, yeah, of course I thought of that.
我当然也想到了
It's the butterflies I'm trying to work out.
我只是想不透蝴蝶到底怎么变的
Oh, for Pete's sake, invisible wire.
还用说吗，钢丝呀
Too obvious.
那太明显了
How many men have you detailed for tonight?
你今晚派了多少人
We have eight men inside, another eight out front.
里面八人，外面八人
Perhaps you'll get another look at your butterflies.
也许你下回再研究蝴蝶吧
Check the last ten rows there.
检查后面十排
You! Don't touch that! Put that down!
你!别碰那东西!把它放下
Ah, Herr Eisenheim.
艾森瀚先生
Who are you and what do you think you're doing?
你是谁，以为自己在做什么?
I'm Chief Inspector Walter Uhl and I'm inspecting your theatre.
我是华特乌尔探长 我正在检查你的剧院
I've seen you perform.
我看过你的表演
Very impressive.
很让人难忘 非常让人印象深刻
How can we help you, Inspector?
有什么指教吗，探长先生
You will be honored to know that the Crown Prince plans
你将很荣幸得知
to attend your performance tonight.
王子殿下今晚将莅临你的演出
The Crown Prince?
王子殿下?
Yes! So, obviously we have to inspect the theatre.
是的，所以我们得做安检
I think that one's a bit small for an assassin, don't you?
刺客可能会嫌那太小，不是吗
Yes, the orange tree.
是的，关于柳橙树
You know, I have seen things like this before
我曾看过类似的演出
but never one like that. Extraordinary.
但和你的完全不同 无人能及
Thank you.
谢谢
I have been puzzling over how it works, especially how the butterflies fly.
我一直想不透怎么变的 尤其是蝴蝶那段
I assure you your secret is safe with me.
我保证会守密
I'm an officer of the law after all, and a bit of an amateur conjourer.
毕竟我是执法人员 私底下也是业余魔术师
Are you really?
你说真的?
Yes. Well, card tricks, coins, uh, slight of hand, yes?
是的，牌戏、钱币，还懂一点手技
But nothing fancy. Perhaps you'll give me a tip?
没啥了不起，也许你能给点提示
Yes, all right. I'll show you one I'm very fond of.
好啊，教你我很喜欢的一招
Are you a gambling man?
你会赌博吗
On occasion, yes.
偶尔会
I will bet you the secret of the orange tree
我以柳橙树的秘诀与你打赌
that I can guess which hand you place this in every time.
我能猜到你放在哪只手
Excellent.
好极了
Put it in your fist, raise your hand against your forehead,
放掌心，手抬起碰一下额头
concentrate on it, form a mental picture.
全神贯注想像一下画面
-Yes. -Have you got it? -Yes.
-好的..  -想好了吗 -是..
Put your hands in front of you.
手伸到前方
It's in your left.
在左手
-Well ! -A lucky guess, perhaps.
-这 ! -只是好运猜到?也许是
You have a confederate who signals you.
有人在旁提示你吧
No. It's more primitive than that.
不，比这简单多了
Uh-huh.
是吗
When you raise your hand to your head, the blood drains from it.
当你抬起手时，血液会往下流
It will be paler every time.
每次都会变白
Oh, oh, I like that very much.
喔，我喜欢这招
Please take it with my compliments.
请你笑纳
Why, thank you. Eh, the blood drains.
当然，谢了 嗯，血往下流
Now, Inspector, if you don't mind,
探长，如果你不介意
I've got to prepare for tonight's performance.
我得准备今晚的演出了
Ah.
哈
Please stand for his Imperial Highness, Crown Prince Leopold.
起立恭迎利奥波德王子殿下
I thought we might end this evening with a discussion of the soul.
今晚的压轴就让我们探讨灵魂
All of the greatest religions speak
伟大的宗教都曾谈到灵魂的存在
of the soul's endurance beyond the end of life.
超越了生死
So, what then does it mean to die?
死亡的意义到底为何?
I need a volunteer from the audience.
我需要一位自愿者上台
Someone not afraid of death. Please, someone?
一位不畏死亡之人 有人吗，请?
I assure you no tragedy will befall you.
我保证不会有悲剧上身
It's an honor, Duchess Von Teschen.
真是荣幸，特森女爵
Do you know me?
?知道我是谁吗
No.
不
You're quite certain that we've never met before?
?确定我们没见过?
Yes, of course.
是的，当然
Now please gaze directly into my eyes. Look nowhere else.
请凝视我的双眼，不要瞄别处
Wave to yourself. Turn in a circle.
朝自己挥手 转个圈
Now, bow to yourself.
现在，向自己鞠躬
Away.
远离
They must have liked you.
他们一定很欣赏你
They've waited for you nearly five minutes.
等了你快五分钟
Your Highness, may I introduce Eisenheim the Illusionist?
殿下，容我为你介绍魔术师艾森瀚
Well done.
表演得好
Thank you for coming. I hope you enjoyed it.
感谢你的莅临，希望你喜欢
Oh, we more than enjoyed it.
我们不只是喜欢而已
Stimulated great debate amongst us, hasn't it?
还引发一阵辩论，不是吗?
Except of course for your assistant, Duchess Von Teschen.
除了你的助手特森女爵
You seemed to have struck her quite speechless.
你似乎把她吓呆了
A feat in itself. Did you hypnotize her?
了不起的技艺，你催眠了她吗?
In a fashion.
一点点
I'd like to learn that trick.
我倒想学这个戏法
Rainier here thinks you have supernatural powers.
瑞纳觉得你有超能力
Do you claim supernatural powers?
你声称你有超能力吗
I've never said anything of that kind.
我从没这么说
Then you won't mind a question or two.
你不介意我问一两个问题吧
Now let's not ruin it.
我们别再煞风景了
You needn't divulge anything I can't guess.
你毋须泄露我猜不到的事情
As you wish.
悉听尊便
Your assistants are behind a mirror somewhere in robes obviously.
你的助手穿上袍子躲在镜子后方
Lights in the frame perhaps to illuminate them, or angled mirrors?
镜镜框里的光线能照出他 还是角镜?
That would be one way to do it.
这是可行方法之一
I think I understand it all except the ghost.
除了幽灵部分我都懂
That was very, very good.
那真的非常非常精彩
Another viewing perhaps?
还会再大驾光临吗
You must come to the Hofburg next time. We'll make an evening of it.
你下次得来霍夫堡皇宫 我们会有个美好的夜晚
That will be my pleasure.
我的荣幸
So be it. Sophie?
那就来吧，是吧，苏菲?
And we'll gather our best minds next time. You'll really have a challenge then.
我下次会召集智囊团 届时你的挑战可大了
Then I'll prepare something special. Perhaps I'll make you disappear.
我会准备特别的演出 也许我会把你变不见
Oh, my God, when he volunteered her I heard the crashing sound
我的老天，他拱她上台时
of money falling on me in piles.
我听到成堆钱币洒在身上的声音
Every lady of means in Vienna will want to get up there with you now.
每位维也纳女人会巴不得与你同台
What a showoff.
他真是爱现
His father would have died if he had seen such a display.
他的父王看到后搞不好会气死
She didn't seem too happy about it either.
她看来似乎也不太高兴
Well, she'd better get used to it.
她最好快习惯
-How's that? -Word is she'll marry him soon.
-怎么回事 -据说她快嫁给他了
-Really? -Taking her chances if you ask me.
-真的吗 -我会说她得自求多福
Why?
怎么说?
He likes to give his lady friends a good thrashing now and again.
他喜欢对女人拳打脚踢
People say he pushed one of them off a balcony
听说他曾把一人推下阳台
just to cover the beating he had given her.
只为了掩饰他曾痛揍过她
For Herr Eisenheim.
艾森瀚先生的信
Hello, Sophie.
?好，苏菲
When I was on the stage, you knew me right away.
我上台时，你马上就认出我了
It took me a moment but, yes, I knew.
想了一下，是的，我的确认出?
You could have said something.
你大可说些话
I thought you'd figure it out eventually.
我认为?总会想到的
Yes, I would have.
是，我该如此
I would have come another night, volunteered,
我该在某夜自愿…
walked right on stage and said hello.
...上台打招呼
And then you'd really have had to move quickly.
那你很快就得打包走人了
I suspect you would have.
我以为?会这么做
I don't understand why.
我不懂
Perhaps for the same reasons you find it prudent to meet in a carriage.
就如同?约在马车碰面的理由
It's just a game I have to play with them.
这是我和他们玩的游戏
I'm followed everywhere.
我走到哪都被跟
It's-it's supposed to be for my protection.
美其名是为了保护我
Yes. So, I hear congratulations are in order.
是的 我听说?有喜讯了?
What for?
为什么
They say you'll be the princess.
大家都说?会当上王妃
It's not decided at all.
根本没这回事
Ah.
是吗
It makes a certain sense, I suppose.
我想也并非不无道理
We've known each other for years and of course our families.
我们已相识许久，彼此家人也是
He's very intelligent. A little too intelligent for his own good.
他非常聪明， 太聪明也不是什么好事
You're lucky, you know. To have broken free as you did.
你很幸运，知道吗?你是自由的
I often wish that I had...
我常希望自己
Wished what?
希望什么
I wished that I would see you again.
我常希望能再见你一面
And now you have.
现在你见到了
Yes, now I have.
是的，我见到了
I look forward to seeing you again at the Hofburg.
我期待在霍夫堡再见到?
Until then.
到时见了
Here's the report on Duchess Von Teschen.
这是特森女爵的报告
Mmm. Anything interesting?
嗯，有啥有趣的?
See for yourself.
你自己看吧
The magician?
那个魔术师?
They drove around for half an hour, then he got out near the theatre.
他们绕了半小时，他先在戏院下车
What do you want us to do?
接下来怎么做?
Join us for a drink?
一起喝一杯?
Please.
请坐
You like something to eat, something to drink, mmm?
想不想吃些什么喝些什么?
No, thank you.
不了，谢谢
Herr Eisenheim, I'm going to ask you a question that may not seem friendly.
艾森瀚先生，我要问你一件事 听起来也许不友善
But I assure you, in fact, is.
但你放心，我其实出于好意
What is your relationship with the Duchess Von Teschen?
你和特森女爵是什么关系
You're right, that doesn't seem friendly.
你没说错，这问题很不友善
Oh, but that is precisely my point.
这正是我的重点
For, you see, where others might judge a discreet carriage ride
你想别人会怎么看马车里的幽会
for what it seemed to be, I am willing to find out what it actually was.
既然表面看来很可疑 我很乐意调查真相
All right. We were childhood acquaintances.
好吧 我们是小时的玩伴
Acquaintances?
玩伴?
Childhood friends. My father was a cabinetmaker.
童年时的朋友 我的父亲是家具工
He made the furniture for her family's house.
他曾为她的家族制作家具
I see, the cabinet maker's son friends with a--
我懂了，家具工之子结交了一位
Has there been a complaint?
有什么人不满吗?
Oh, no, no.
喔，不，不
If there'd been a complaint...
如果真有什么不满
Well, we'd be having a very, uh, different sort of conversation.
我们就不会这样对话了
Yes. He relies on you for that sort of thing, does he?
他都靠你处理这类事，不是吗
I'm a simple public servant, Herr Eisenheim.
我只是单纯的公仆，艾森瀚
That's not what I hear.
我听到的不是如此
I hear you'll be the Chief of Police very soon.
我听说你快当上警察总长
Maybe Mayor of Vienna? Party Secretary?
还是维也纳市长?议事大臣?
All subject to his whim.
他说了才算
You better hope he doesn't dissolve the Parliament before you get there.
你最好希望他解散国会时 是在你升官之后
Now, the Prince has some progressive ideas, but he will make a fine Emperor.
王子殿下有些想法很先进 但他会是一位好君主
Well, they say you're very close to him, so I'm sure you'll be fine.
听说你们关系良好 我确信你会很好
Look-- Yes, indeed, they say that I'm very close to the Prince.
是的，大家都说我与王子关系好
But the simple truth of the matter is, Herr Eisenheim,
事实摆在眼前，艾森瀚
I'm the son of a butcher.
我是肉贩之子
He's the heir to the Empire.
他是王位继承人
How close could we be to such as him, Hmm?
我和他能好到哪去?
Do you see my point?
你清楚我的重点吗
Don't fool yourself that you can play in their game.
别傻到以为你可和他们打交道
I've served on the edge of it for many, many years
我在底下服务，做了很多很多年
and I can tell you with certainty there's no trick they haven't seen.
我很确定他们看遍各种手法
It's not worth it.
这样做不值得
My guest tonight is not a showman at all, but rather a wizard
今晚的贵客不是表演家，而是巫师
who has sold his soul to the devil in return for unholy powers.
他用灵魂与恶魔交换邪恶力量
Or so at least some of our friends here would have us believe.
或者有人要让我们如此相信
But fear not, everything can and will be explained.
别害怕，所有事情都有解释
All mysteries penetrated.
所有的谜团都能破解
Here, Here. Well said. Well said.
嘿!说的好，说的好
Is that the emperor?
那是国王吗?
Ah, yes, your father.
是的，你的父亲
I didn't think he was invited .
我不知道他也受邀了
A fair likeness of the old man.
很像那位老头
Too modern a style for him, of course.
但没那么时髦
I'm afraid I'm not much of a painter.
恐怕我不是一位好画家
It's true, there are no brush strokes in this painting,
没错，画上没有笔触痕迹
I can see that clearly.
我看得出来
So to achieve the color some sort of chemical must be interacting, presumably.
上色效果 应是某种化学物质的作用
Some sort of sprayer up your sleeve? May I?
袖子里有喷雾器吗?可以看看?
If you feel you must.
如果你觉得有必要
I do.
的确有必要
Oh, let the man do his show.
就让他好好表演吧
You want me to just sit there when it's so obvious?
事实摆在眼前，?竟要我呆坐?
I do.
我是这么希望
He tries to trick you. I try to enlighten you.
他试着要愚弄?，而我要启迪?
Which is the more noble pursuit?
谁的目的比较高尚?
May we have the lights please, so his Highness can better see?
可以打光让王子看得更清楚吗
See here, Leopold, let's have a show.
利奥波德，让我们看秀
Here, here.
嘿!嘿!
Come on, Leopold, get on with it.
得了，利奥波德，继续吧
Very well, I propose a challenge.
好，我要下挑战
Why don't you astonish us, if you can, without all the gadgetry?
你能不靠这些机关使我们吃惊吗
As you wish.
如你所愿
Your sword is very beautiful. Might I see it?
你的剑很漂亮，能让我看看吗
Certainly.
当然
May I?
不介意吧?
Where does power flow from?
力量源自何处?
Skill or destiny, or divine right?
技巧?命运还是天意?
We all know the story of a sword called Excalibur.
我们都听过石中剑的故事
Excalibur's blade was fixed in stone, and there it stayed.
它插在石缝中静止不动
Many worthy knights tried to pull the sword from the stone.
许多伟大的武士都尝试拔剑
Only Arthur succeeded proving his right to rule.
亚瑟证明了他的正当性
Who can take this sword? You sir, can you take the sword?
谁拔得起剑? 这位先生，你能否拔起这把剑?
No surprise there.
一点都不让人意外
Perhaps you, sir.
也许你可以，先生
Not so eager, cousin.
不用这么急切，表弟
You shall live a long life.
你会很长寿
Thank you for your indulgence.
谢谢你的投入
Come now, if you can't pull it out you'll never be Emperor.
如果你拔不出，永远别想当上国王
Your father will live to be a hundred.
你的父亲会活到一百岁
The sword to its rightful owner!
这把剑的真正主人出现了
That's enough light entertainment for this evening.
今晚的余兴节目到此为止
For more serious discussion, please join me for a drink.
还有更严肃的话题，请与我共饮
Shut him down.
把他的表演停掉
Well, he's very popular, your Highness.
他很受欢迎，王子殿下
I'm sure you'll find a way.
我确定你会有办法
What did you do to him?
你对他做了什么
I gave him what he asked for.
我给他想要的
What would possess you to do something so foolish?
你为何鬼迷心窍做这种蠢事?
Duchess Von Teschen, you must come along, my dear.
亲爱的特森女爵，?得过来
We don't want to keep the Prince waiting. Did you enjoy the show?
我们不能让王子久候，喜欢表演吗
It was wonderful, wasn't it?
棒极了，不是吗
It was amusing.
很有娱乐性
Who told you where to find me?
谁告诉?到哪找我
Your manager.
你经理
I told him if he wants to stay in Vienna, you need my help.
他如想留在维也纳，要我帮忙
Ah, so I'm to be driven from the city, is that it?
所以我要被赶出这城市吗
Good, I shall relish it.
很好，再好不过
Stop it! I came here to try to help you.
别说了! 我是来这里帮你的
Why! Why should you possibly care what happens to me now?
为什么??何必在乎我的事?
You were my friend. I am your friend.
你是我的朋友，我也是你的朋友
We knew each other very briefly a long time ago.
我们只是在很久以前短暂相识
You don't know me at all.
?根本就不了解我
Then why did you speak to me? Why did you even bother talking-
你何必与我说话?何必自找麻烦?
And you kept it all this time.
?一直都戴在身上
I used to sit and stare at your picture trying to imagine where you were.
我常望着你的照片，想像你的去处
At night I'd have dreams I had gone with you,
我梦见我和你离开，直到醒来
and then I'd wake up and realize where I was.
才意识到自己身在何方
But in my dreams you had shorter hair and no beard.
我梦中的你 头发短了点，也没胡须
Where did you go when you left?
你当时离开后去了哪
To my uncle's farm near Prague.
我叔叔在布拉格附近的农场
How exotic.
多有异国情调啊
I went to Russia, then Asia Minor, and then the Orient for many years.
在俄国、小亚细亚与东方待了多年
So long.
去了真久
I always meant to return.
我一直想回来，只是
I just- I kept thinking I'd find it around the next corner.
我不断想着也许能在下一处发现
What?
发现什么?
A real mystery.
真正的奥秘
I saw remarkable things, but the only mystery
我看到很不凡的事物 但唯一解不开的奥秘就是我的心
I never solved was why my heart couldn't let go of you.
为何忘不了?
He wants me to go to Budapest with him next week to announce our engagement.
他希望我去布达佩斯 下周与他同行并宣布订婚
He wants the Hungarians behind him. They're going to crown him King.
他要匈牙利人做后盾他们要拥他为王
I'm sure his father will have something to say about that.
他的父亲想必会很有意见
He plans to overthrow his father.
他计画推翻自己的父王
That could go very badly for him... and for you.
这对他很不利 对?也是
You shouldn't be involved.
?不该涉入其中
I am part of his plan.
我是他计画中的一部份
He only gets Hungary by aligning himself with my family.
要匈牙利人支持 得靠我们两家结盟
Leave him.
离开他
It's not that easy.
没那么容易
Call it off and come away with me.
取消婚事和我走
Or don't say anything and we'll just go.
或者现在一走了之
As long as we are alive he'll hunt us.
只要我们活着，他会追捕我们
And when he finds us he'll kill us.
若被他找到会杀死我们的
Look at me. Do you truly want to leave with me?
看着我，?真的想与我离开?
Yes, I do.
是的，我愿意
There you are. As I predicted they shut us down.
你在这 我早料到我们要关门大吉了
Are you happy now, hmm? You made your point.
你满意了吧?你表达立场了
It doesn't matter that we were sold out for the whole run.
票房满不满座对你根本不重要
No, look. You got it off your chest.
你终于一吐为快了
Do we have money?
我们有钱吗
What?
什么
Do we have any money saved?
我们还有存款吗
Yes, we have some. But we could have had much, much more.
是，还有一些，本来还能有更多的
Mmm, it will have to do.
嗯，应该能派上用场
And the second account, all of it.
还有第二个户头里的，全部都要
Of course, Herr Eisenheim.
是的，艾森瀚先生
Thank you.
谢谢
And you have no doubt it was Duchess Von Teschen?
你确定那是特森女爵吗?
I'd stake my life on it.
可以拿我的生命担保
What was in the suitcase?
箱子里有什么?
I don't know.
我不知道
He's by the first car.
他在第一台车厢
The map will show you where to meet.
地图会告诉你到哪碰面
When it's done, you'll travel ahead with her and I shall follow.
完事后，你和她先走，我会跟上
And she understands everything this entails?
她清楚这件事的后果吗
Completely. There's not a lot of time.
完全清楚，时间不多了
As you know, we sometimes follow Duchess Von Teschen for her protection.
你知道，我们会跟踪并保护女爵
Yesterday she was seen in the company of another man.
昨天她与另一男人碰面
What man?
什么人?
Eisenheim, the Illusionist.
艾森瀚那位魔术师
What were they doing?
他们当时在做什么
Well, they were meeting and, uh--
他们见了面，然后
Touching? Kissing? Were they fucking?
抚摸?亲吻?还是搞在一起?
Not that we observed, no.
就我们观察没有，然而我相信
However, I have reason to believe that they may be planning something together.
他们可能一同计画某事
It's possible they may be leaving.
可能是两人要离开
I'm not certain of anything yet, your Highness.
什么都还不明确，殿下
Thank you, Inspector.
谢谢你，探长
We can of course acquire more information-
我们会再L集更多情报
He spent the afternoon in Vienna with his father.
他下午在维也纳陪父亲
He's expected shortly.
他等会才到
What a surprise. I thought you didn't like it here.
真让人意外，我以为?讨厌这里
I suppose you think you're very clever
?大概自以为很聪明又自主
and very democratic in your friendships, aren't you?
尤其在交友方面，不是吗
What are you talking about?
你到底在说什么
Your magician friend. I know you've been with him.
?的魔术师朋友，?和他有往来
It's true. We've been friends since childhood.
没错，我们从小就是朋友
You sleep with all your childhood friends?
?和所有童年玩伴上床吗
I will not be spoken to this way.
这种态度我不回答
You'll be spoken to as I wish to speak to you.
只要我想问，?就得回答
You're drunk.
你喝醉了
You're getting quite old, aren't you?
?老大不小了，不是吗
You know, my mother was sixteen years old when she married my father.
我的母亲十六岁时嫁给我的父亲
And you? Can you even bear children?
?还生得出孩子吗，有什么用处
Are you any use at all? Are you trying to embarrass me?
?想让我难堪吗
It has nothing to do with you.
与你无关
It has everything to do with me!
与我关系可大了!
You will not share my bed if you've slept with him!!
如果?和他睡过，别想上我的床
You don't understand. I'm not going to share your bed at all.
你不懂，我根本不想与你同床
I'm not going to Budapest with you.
我不会和你去布达佩斯
I don't want to be part of what you're planning.
我不要被你利用
And I will not marry you.
也不会嫁给你
I assume you haven't been so stupid as to tell him anything.
我假设?没蠢到告诉他任何事
'Cause if you disrupt my plans
要是?坏了我的好事
I will have no further use for you, do you understand?
?也没好处 明白吗?
Now, you will travel to Budapest tomorrow.
准备明天去布达佩斯
I recommend that you are here early packed and ready to go.
我建议?赶快打包准备上路
Do nothing more to embarrass me.
别再丢我的脸
Goodbye.
再见
What do you mean "goodbye"?
"再见"是什么意思
Come back here.
给我回来!
Don't disobey me again. Whore!
别再忤逆我，婊子
Out of my way. Please, don't-- Uugh.
让开，求求你，不要
No, leave that. Leave all the lanterns.
不用了，放着吧，提灯都留下
Duchess Von Tuschen!
特森女爵!
Over here!
在这里!
I thought you saw her get on the train with him!
我以为你看到她和他上了火车
No, sir, we were waiting in Vienna for them.
不，我们在维也纳
But they left from Barden?. We assumed she was him.
他们从巴登上车
Should I wire the Crown Prince in Budapest?
我们把她认成他
It's been done! Who are you?
该发电报给王子吗
I'm the family's doctor. Are you the Chief Inspector?
发了!你是谁?
Yes, I am.
我是她的家庭医师，你是探长吗?
You understand this is a police matter now?
我是，你知道这是警方的事吗
Of course I understand.
我当然了解
Good, good.
好，好
You have determined the cause of death?
你判定死因了吗
She bled to death.
失血过多
There's a wound on her throat just above the left collarbone-
伤口在左锁骨上方咽喉
Uh, some knife or sword.
可能是匕首或剑
May I take a look?
我能看一眼吗
Inspector, l-I will not stand for it.
探长，这我不能认同
The Crown Prince will not stand for it. This is not some circus sideshow.
王子也不会认可的 这不是马戏表演
My apologies, of course.
抱歉，你没错
Thank you, doctor.
谢谢你，医生
Probably robbed. Gypsies maybe?
可能是被抢了，也许是吉普赛人?
Saw all those diamonds, couldn't say no.
看看这些钻石，不是不可能
Chief Inspector, there's one thing you should know.
探长，有件事该让你知道
Yes, what is that?
是的，什么事
In the folds of her dress I found this small gemstone.
我在她衣内发现这颗小宝石
Seen last Thursday at 7:30 p.m. riding without
她上周四七点半独自骑着马
an escort toward the Imperial Hunting Lodge.
到皇家狩猎小屋
Groomsman said she arrived about 8:30.
古仕曼说她抵达时间约八点半
What was she doing riding alone?
她独自一人要做什么
He did this. You know he did.
他干的，你知道是他干的
I know who did what?
我知道谁做了什么?
The Crown Prince! He killed her. He's done it before and you know it!
王子!他杀了她! 他有前科，你清楚得很
No, I don't know that. In fact, I'm sure he didn't. He's in Budapest.
不，我不知道 我确定不是，他人在布达佩斯
He killed her before he left.
他在动身前杀了她
I'm afraid the facts don't support your theory.
恐怕事实无法支持你的假设
She was leaving him.
她本来要离开他
For who? You? Yes.
为了谁?你吗 是的
Don't be absurd, Herr Eisenheim.
别荒谬了，艾森瀚
He killed her because he couldn't let her go.
他杀她是因为不让她走
She knew his secret.
她知道他的秘密
What secret?
什么秘密
Ask your Inspector. He knows.
问你的探长，他知道
Stop this right now!
别再说了
Are you completely corrupt?
你完全堕落了吗
No, not completely, no, which is
不，就是因为不完全，我建议你
why I'll advise you not to accuse anyone especially his Imperial Highness,
不要指控任何人，尤其是王子
or you'll end up in jail yourself.
否则你就等着老死狱中吧
Where's the guard who let her out of the gate?
让她离开城门的守卫在哪
Gone with the Crown Prince.
王子殿下带走了
Did any of the servants see her leave?
任何仆人看到她离开吗
All asleep.
当时都睡了
What about him?
那他呢
He uh, he put her horse in the first stall when she arrived.
他替她把马牵到第一个马厩
This one?
这一个?
We don't have jurisdiction on imperial property.
我们无权过问皇家所有物
Thank you. I know.
谢谢，我知道
So, what are you doing?
你在做什么
Investigating.
查案
Listening to that magician, are you? For all we know, he did it.
你也听到魔术师说的 就我们所知，是他干的
No, I think not.
不，我不这么认为
The Crown Prince-- He's back.
王子殿下回来了
Chief Inspector, we should go. Now.
探长，我们该走了，就是现在
And what have you found out?
你查到什么
She was last seen riding here alone.
有人目击她曾独自骑马
Yes, and based on your information I then threw her out, Chief?.
根据你的资料，是我赶她出去的
Did she commit suicide?
她是自杀吗
No, it was surely murder.
不，这是一宗谋杀案
Do you have a suspect?
有任何嫌疑犯吗
We will soon, your Highness.
很快会有的，王子殿下
Later that week, we arrested a man and charged him with murder.
接下来，我们逮捕一人并控告谋杀
But I knew that that wouldn't satisfy Eisenheim.
我知道艾森瀚不会就此服气
I had my men continue to watch him.
我让手下继续监视他
He finally emerged from his grief and bought a rundown theatre.
他终于走出伤痛，买下一间老戏院
It's perfect.
太完美了
He fired his manager and began preparing for a new kind of show.
他开除经理人，并准备新表演
Who is he?
他是谁
My name is Frankel.
我的名字是法兰柯
Where did you come from?
你从哪来的
I come from Brunn. My father is a lens grinder there.
我来自布隆，父亲是一位镜片磨工
How did you come to be here tonight?
你今晚如何来此
I don't know.
我不知道
Are you alive?
你还活着吗
What can you tell us about the other side?
能否说说另一个世界?
What's it like?
什么样子?
Yes, tell us.
是呀，跟我们说
You must know things, secret things.
你一定知道什么秘密
They don't seem to think it's a trick.
他们似乎不认为这是唬人的
Eisenheim's audience had always been enthusiastic.
艾森瀚的观众向来很热烈
But now he was attracting a more impassioned following.
他又吸引一批更激情的拥护者
Madame, please.
女士，麻烦?了
With these spirts, these manifestations,
藉这些灵魂与表演，艾森瀚证明了
Eisenheim has given us hard proof of the soul's immortality.
灵魂的不朽与灵体的再现
A spirit has been reaffirmed in the face of modern scientific materialism.
能以现代科学唯物论的面貌呈现
The work of spiritualism will arouse humanity to a new moral earnestness.
招魂术召回了人性的新道德良知
It is a revolutionary movement
这是一场革命运动
and we will turn the empire into a spiritual republic.
我们能让帝国改制成崇高的共和国
Do you think Eisenheim's behind all this?
你认为艾森瀚是幕后指使者吗?
Why must I be bothered with a magician?
为何得让一位魔术师来烦我
He has proven to be more than a magician, your Highness.
他不是一般的魔术师，王子殿下
He is a charlatan. He's a faker.
他是个术士、骗子
If he pretends to have supernatural I powers put him on trial for fraud.
如果他伪装超能力，就以诈欺关他
First we have to show it as fraud then do it
首先我们得证明 那是骗局然后做他
find out how the trick is done and then arrest him.
查出怎么变的然后逮他
This is just a rough demonstration, Inspector.
这只是很粗糙的示范，探长
But you can see how it could work.
但你可看出它怎么办到
Yes, I see. Not bad. Not bad.
是的，我懂了，还不错
We need a spy in Eisenheim's troop.
我们得从艾森瀚那找位内应
Those Orientals, yhey won't give us anything.
那些东方人都不肯说
I already tried.
我试过了
Then try something else.
那就想别的办法呀
What has happened here?
发生了什么事
One of those ghosts from the theatre, down the street.
有个戏院的鬼魂在街道上
Where!
哪里
Right there, and it's a boy.
就在那，还是个小男孩
Sick.
真令人作呕
Where is this thing?
那东西在哪
Over there.
那里
Did you see it?
你看到了吗
It was right over there.
就在那里
Where are you taking him?
你要带他去哪
I want to know how it's done.
我要知道怎么做的
First the orange tree, now this.
先是柳橙树，现在是这个
Do I have to share all my professional secrets with the police?
我得和警方分享我的商业机密码
Well, in this case, yes. Or I'll be forced to arrest you.
这回由不得你，否则我得逮捕你
On what charge?
什么罪名
Mmm, well, we'll start with fraud.
先是诈欺
Excuse me, Chief Inspector.
恕我打断，探长
What!
怎么了
I think you should look outside the window.
你应该看一下窗外
Who are they?
他们是谁
They are here for him.
他们都是为他而来的
Ah, my goodness, you have a devoted following.
你信众真死忠
What is it they expect of you?
他们在期望什么
I have no idea. What do your spies tell you?
我不知道，你的密探没告诉你?
That you plan to separate? the monarchy perhaps?
也许是你计画要分裂君主政体?
Why?
为什么?
Just because the Crown Prince is a murderer?
因为王子是杀人凶手?
He's not a murderer.
他没杀人
We have the real murderer in prison. He pleaded guilty.
凶手已入狱认罪了
You've got the wrong man.
你们抓错人了
You don't know that.
你根本就不清楚状况
No, but you do.
但你很清楚
Herr Eisenheim, you will also go to prison
艾森瀚，你也会进监牢
if you don't explain to me what it is you are doing.
如果你还是不愿解释你的作为
The sentence will be greater if that mob attacks the building.
如有群众攻击这里，判刑更重
Well?
哎
What are you doing? Stop! Stop!
你在做什么?停下来
Listen to me, please. You must listen to me, please.
请你们听我说
Thank you all for coming.
谢谢你们前来
I've been speaking with the Chief Inspector,
我已经与探长谈过，我认为
and I think there's been a serious misunderstanding.
有个很大的误会
I want you all to know that everything
你们该知道
that you have seen in my theatre is an illusion.
在我剧院里出现的是幻象
It's a trick. It's not real.
是魔术，那是假的
I can't bring loved ones back from the grave.
我无法召回亡魂
I can't receive messages from the other side.
我不能接收另一世界的讯息
I apologize if I've given you any false hope.
抱歉，我不该让你们误会
My intention has only been to entertain.
我目的只是娱乐
Nothing more.
仅止于此
Now I appreciate your support, but you must go home.
谢谢你们的支持，回家吧
Please, you must go.
拜?你们，走吧
There, now I've explained it. So it can't be fraud. May I go?
我解释过就不算诈欺 能走了吗
Has he tricked you? Is that it?
他也唬住你了吗?
No, your Highness.
不，王子殿下
Then why are you failing me?
那为何让我失望?
I thought I could trust you.
我以为我能信任你
I thought you were a man I could bring with me when I took the throne.
我以为我登基时可以提拔你
Am I wrong about you?
我看错你了吗
No. You're not wrong, your Highness, no.
不，你没错，王子殿下
I need men who can complete the tasks assigned to them!!
我需要能圆满达成任务之人
Instead I'm surrounded by fools.
我身边都是笨蛋
In the end I must do everything myself.
最后总要我自己出马
I can see this case will be no different.
这回也不会有何不同
How do I look?
我看起来如何
Ordinary, your Highness, very ordinary.
很像一般人，王子殿下，非常一般
I think I'm going to enjoy this.
我想我会乐在其中
They don't recognize you.
他们认不出你
Good. Now keep your distance. I don't want to be seen with a policeman.
好，离远点，我不想和警察站一起
Who are you?
?是谁
Are you Duchess Von Teschen?
?是特森女爵吗
Yes.
是的
What's happened to you?
?发生什么事
She was murdered. Were you murdered?
她是被谋杀的 ?是被谋杀的吗
By who? Did they arrest the right man?
谁下的手 他们抓的是对的人吗
Tell us, please. Who murdered you?
请告诉我们，谁杀了?
Someone... here.
某人就在这里
Tell us, point him out. Was it the Crown Prince?
告诉我们，把他指出来 是王子吗?
He's killed a woman before!
他曾杀过一个女人
Word? the Crown Prince isn't even here.
王子又不在这
The Crown Prince killed her! Something must be done!
王子杀了她!一定有事发生
Chief Inspector, are you sure you have the right man?
探长，你确定你抓对人了吗
Quite sure. Excuse me.
相当确定，让我过一下
Did you investigate the Crown Prince?
你调查过王子吗
He cannot continue if this is true. He must be brought to justice.
如果真是他，他该受到正义制裁
It's not true, the magic trick is not evidence. What is your name?
不是真的，魔术不能当证据 你名字是?
I don't see how that matters.
这有什么关系?
I advise you to watch what you say, sir.
那建议你谨言慎行，先生
That actress didn't even look like Sophie.
那个女演员根本不像苏菲
But the audience is stupid and he knows it.
观众真蠢
He manipulates them. He himself said nothing.
他操纵了他们，自己却什么都不说
His actress said nothing inflammatory.
女演员也没说什么
He left it to the audience to make their accusations.
他让台下观众自行做出指控
All taunts paid for by him, of course.
那些起\的人也是他买通的
I don't suppose you made a note of those people?
你没记下那些人是谁吧
I'm afraid we didn't have enough men tonight.
恐怕今晚人手不够
At the next performance I want them all arrested,
下次表演时，我要他们通通就逮
every one of them-Eisenheim and the whole troupe.
艾森瀚与他的同夥
I want to have an example made of him in front of all his followers.
我要拿他来杀鸡儆猴
That was very foolish last night. You can't destroy him, you know.
你昨晚真愚蠢，你毁不了他的
You can't bring down the monarchy.
你无法扳倒君主政体
Oh, I know I can't.
我知道我不行
Then don't raise her again! Don't provoke those questions.
那就别再召唤她，不要挑起问题
Herr Eisenheim, I don't want to arrest you.
艾森瀚，我不想抓你
I'm a cynical man, God knows.
我很愤世嫉俗
But if your manifestations are somehow real-
即使你的表演是真的，我承认
and even I'm willing to admit you're a very special person,
你是很特别的人，即使只是戏法
and if it's a trick then it's equally impressive--
我也得说它令人印象深刻
Either way you have a gift, so don't make me put you in jail.
无论如何，你很有天分 不要逼我抓你
Promise me you won't do it again.
答应我不会再有下次
I promise you you'll enjoy this next show.
我答应你会喜欢接下来的演出
What do you want?
你到底要什么
Nothing.
什么都不要
Then why bring her back?
那为何带她回来
Just to be with her.
只想与她在一起
To be with her.
与她在一起
-Everything is ready? -Yes, sir.
-都准备好了吗 -是的，长官
We're trying to assess how he might escape.
我们正在预测他会怎么逃跑
He will not escape! I want guards at every door and window!
他逃不了，每道门窗都要有人看守
Sir.
是的
I want to apologize to you for my behavior of late.
我要为我最近的举止道歉
But I want to make it up to you if you'll listen to a proposition.
我想补偿你，希望你听听这个提议
Well, I don't know.
这我不知道
I'll make it worth your while, Josef.
我会让你值回票价的，约瑟
You know, I'm very busy right now.
我现在很忙，我可不是
I haven't just been sitting around waiting for you.
闲闲没事做，等着你来
No, no, of course.
不，你当然不是
I want you to assume control of all my finances and my assets.
我要你接管我所有的金钱与财物
Everything.
全部?
Yes, including this theatre
是的，包括这间剧院
and all the receipts from tonight's performance,
和今晚的收入
which I offer with my sincere thanks.
这是我最诚挚的谢意
What do you say?
你意下如何
All right, I'll do it.
好吧，我答应
Good. Good.
很好
Would you like me to introduce you tonight?
你要我介绍你出场吗
No. Tonight just enjoy the show.
不，今晚就好好欣赏演出吧
Excuse me, Chief Inspector, I'm Josef Fischer, Eisenheim's manager.
探长，我是约瑟费雪 艾森瀚的经理
Yes, I remember.
我记得
What's going on? Why all the police?
发生什么事?怎么都是警察
Precautions, Herr Fischer, precautions.
只是预防措施，费雪先生
Are you planning to arrest Eisenheim?
你计画逮捕艾森瀚吗
That's entirely up to him.
这就取决于他了
It's Duchess Von Teschen.
那是特森女爵
Why were you murdered?
?为何被谋杀
I was leaving him.
我要离开他
Leaving who?
离开谁
The Crown Prince?
王子吗
Of course it was the Crown Prince.
当然是王子殿下了
We won't stand for it!
这我们可不能忍受
I tried to get away.
我试着逃跑
I was wearing my locket when I died but now it's gone.
我死时戴着项?，现在却弄丢了
It's lost.
不见了
Tell us, please, who murdered you?
请告诉我们，是谁杀了??
Was it the Crown Prince?
是王子殿下吗
We must do something!
我们得做些什么
Get up!
行动!
In the name of his Imperial Majesty and the city of Vienna,
我代表国王陛下与维也纳市
I hereby arrest Eduard Abramovitz,
逮捕爱德华艾维兹
also known as Eisenheim the Illusionist,
魔术师艾森瀚
on charges of disturbing public order, charlatanism,
罪名是妨害公共秩序，诈欺
and threats against the empire!
以及危害国家安全
Find him!
找到他!
Where is he?
他人在哪
He was right there.
他刚才还在那里
-How is his trick done? -No trick.
-他的戏法怎么变的 -不是戏法
How is it done!
怎么变的?
I don't know. Nobody knows.
我不知道，没人知道
Dammit!
该死!
I had my driver take the sword to police headquarters.
我请随从把剑送到警察总署
My men will examine it and see
我的手下会检查宝石
if it matches the gemstone found on Duchess Von Teschen's body.
与女爵身上的是否相符
I have no doubt that it will.
我想不会错
And after that, I came in here and you asked me why I was late.
接着我进来，你问我为何迟到
You've stolen Imperial property.
你偷了皇家的财产
That seems trivial compared with murder.
和谋杀相比简直无足轻重
Even if that were true, you have no jurisdiction here.
就算是真的，也不属于你的管辖
That's right.
是的
You may do as you wish here without consequence.
你可以无所忌惮
Nobody can punish you, except one man.
没人能处罚你，但有一人例外
Who's that?
是谁
The Emperor.
国王
I don't suppose he'll leave his crown to a murderer, do you?
他不会传位给杀人凶手 你杀了人吗?
He'll never believe you.
他不会相信你的
Maybe not.
也许
But I wrote a letter to his general staff telling them everything.
但我写信给参谋和盘托出
Including your plan to overthrow the Emperor.
包括你意图谋反的计画
I know they'll listen to that.
他们会重视这件事
You'll not take the throne, not with my help.
你当不上国王的，我帮不了你
You no longer want to be Chief of Police?
你不想当警察总长
Mayor of Vienna?
维也纳市长?
You don't want to be a baron, an aristocrat?
也不想封爵或贵族?
I'm afraid that's out of the question at this point.
恐怕这不是目前的重点
You fool, he's tricking you. He's manipulating you.
你这蠢蛋，他在耍你，在利用你
He had the sword at the command performance.
他在表演时曾拿过剑
He could have pried the stones loose then and planted them here.
他大可撬松宝石，用来裁赃
-He's planted everything. -You were drunk..
-他策划所有一切 -你喝醉了..
It's all a trick. It's an illusion.
一切都是戏法，一切都是假象
Perhaps there's truth in this illusion.
假象背后也许就是真相
You need to wire your driver and have the sword returned.
你得拍电报给随从，把剑拿回来
Or what?
不然怎样
I'll shoot you. Perhaps I'll shoot you anyway.
我会杀了你 也许我到头来都会杀你
And then you'll have killed a police inspector and a Duchess.
那你就杀了一位警探与女爵
Or perhaps you'll kill yourself.
或者你该自杀
You, uh, committed suicide, distraught at having failed your leader.
你因办事不力而自我了断
Ah, some officers of the general staff I'd guess.
我想是参谋部的人
They must've received my letter.
他们应该已收到我的信
What do you want?
你到底要什么
I don't want anything.
我什么都不要
Fine. Fine. You shall have nothing.
很好，你也不配得到
Gentlemen.
各位男士
The situation is so obvious.
明显地
Everyone's completely incompetent.
这里全是一群饭桶
My father runs the Empire into the ground and no one notices.
我的父亲治国无方却没人发现
No one does anything about it.
没有人有所行动
I propose to cleanup the mess and you thank me by betraying me.
我想整顿，你们却以背叛回报
Well, you're all becoming irrelevant. You'll all be replaced.
你们都不重要了，你们会被取代
The country will be run by mongrels.
这国家将由杂种治理
A thousand different voices screaming to be heard and nothing will be done!
不同意见在呐喊着 却无人闻问
Nothing!
无人闻问
I've done everything I can!
我已尽力了
Too much! Far too much.
太尽力了
Your Highness, are you in there? Your Highness, open door.
殿下，你在里面吗?开门
Please, open the door.
请你开门
By your father's authority I insist you open the door.
奉国王之令，我希望你开门
You must open the door!
你必须开门
You're all fools...
你们这些笨蛋
Please, your Highness.
请开门，殿下
And I can't stand it. I won't stand it.
我受不了了，我再也受不了了
Break down the door. Break it down!
把门撞开
What happened?
发生什么事?
The Crown Prince just shot himself.
王子殿下刚才自杀了
Are you Chief Inspector Uhl?
你是乌尔探长吗
I used to be.
我曾经是
You! Who gave you this! Who gave you this!
你!是谁给你的，是谁
Herr, Eisenheim!
艾森瀚
When!
何时给的
All aboard!
全部上车!
Tickets and papers.
车票与文件
When it's done...
事情完成之后
...you'll travel ahead with her and I shall follow.
你和她先走，我随后会跟上
And she understands everything this entails?
她清楚这件事的后果吗
Completely.
完全清楚
Do you think Eisenheim's behind all this?
你认为艾森瀚是幕后指使者吗
So, what does it mean to die?
死亡的意义到底为何
What do you want?
你到底要什么
To be with her.
和她在一起
Chief Inspector, there's one thing you should know.
探长，有件事该让你知道
Your sword is very beautiful. Might I see it?
您的剑真漂亮，能让我看看吗?
You're drunk.
你喝醉了
He's a charlatan and he's a faker.
他是术士、骗子
He's plotted everything.
一切都是他策划的
Everything you have seen is an illusion.
你看到的都是幻象
It's a trick.
一切都是魔术